National University Extension Association (NUEA) Records
National University Extension Association (NUEA) Records
- Part 2
  - U.S. Office of Education, Adult Basic Education, Teacher Training Institute
    - 1966 Regional Institues
      - University of Missouri at Kansas City (2) (Box 49)
      - University of Missouri at Kansas City, Programmed Instruction (Box 49)
      - University of Texas (Box 49)
      - Wayne State University (Box 49)
    - 1967
      - ABE in Yonkers, Optimal Program Plan (Box 50)
      - Administration (Box 50)
      - Administration, Memoranda (3) (Box 50)
      - "Adult Basic Education for the Disadvantaged"-- John McKee (Box 50)
      - Annual Meeting (Box 50)
      - Background Statement (Box 50)
      - Bibliographies (Box 50)
      - Bibliography for Administrators and Teachers (Box 50)
      - Business Concepts (Box 50)
      - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1967-1968 (Box 50)
      - Clipping (Box 50)
      - Conference Room Dedication (Box 50)
      - Conferences -- Southeastern Conference, April 20-21 (Box 50)
      - Consultants (Box 51)
      - Contact Lists (2) (Box 51)
      - Correspondence (2), See also General Correspondence
        - Administration (2) (Box 51)
        - Gerald A. Foster (Box 51)
        - Hy Hoffman, 1967-1968 (Box 51)
        - Lynn Mack (1) (Box 51)
        - Lynn Mack (2) (Box 52)
        - Derek Nunney (Box 52)
        - Joseph C. Paige (Box 52)
        - Requests for Publications (2) (Box 52)
        - James J. Ryan (Box 52)
      - Curriculum Guide, 1967-1968 (Box 52)
      - Curriculum Guide for ABE for Personal and Family Development (Box 52)
      - Curriculum Guides (Box 52)
      - Curriculum Meeting (Box 52)
      - Directory -- ABE Institutes (Box 52)
      - Educational Psychology Associates Report, Evaluation and Documentation (Box 52)
      - Educational Psychology Associates Report, Evaluation and Documentation (with photographs) (Box 53)
      - Educational Technology (3) (Box 53)
      - Educational Technology, Report -- Pre-Institute Seminar (Box 53)
      - Evaluation Report (2) (Box 53)
      - Evaluation Report, Abstract (Box 53)
      - Federal Roster (Box 53)
      - Field Interviews (Box 53)
      - Final Report (Box 54)
      - Final Report, Guidelines and Data (2) (Box 54)
      - Finance (Box 54)
      - Finance -- Anticipated Expenses (Box 54)
      - Finance, Financial Reports (2) (Box 54)
      - Financial Statements (Box 54)
      - Forms, General (Box 54)
      - Furniture Management Center (Box 54)
      - General Correspondence (Box 54)
        See also Correspondence
      - General Correspondence (3) (Box 55)
      - General Correspondence (A-I) (Box 55)
      - Grant
        - Contract and Proposal (Box 55)
        - Contract Renewal (Box 55)
        - Evaluation and other Materials (exhibits) (Box 56)
        - Extension Data (Box 56)
        - Revisions (Box 56)
      - Information and Materials List (Box 56)
      - Memoranda (Box 56)
      - NAPSAE (2)
        - Manual of Training Materials (Box 56)
        - NAPSAE-NUEA meeting, June 29 (Box 56)
        - Report of Evaluation Committee (Box 56)
      - National ABE Conference, Sept. 28-29 (Box 56)
      - National Curriculum Meeting, Background Statement (Box 56)
      - National Curriculum Meeting, March 6-7 (Box 56)
      - National Training Meeting, March 16-17 (Box 56)
      - New Careers Training Program (Box 57)
      - Nunney, Dr. (Box 57)
      - Participants (4)
        - ABE Institutes (Box 57)
        - Allocations, Two and Three Week Institutes (Box 57)
        - Allocations and Assignments (Box 58)
        - Changes (Box 58)
        - Participants and Associates, Breakdown by Sex (Box 58)
      - Position Papers, Bill Barron (Box 58)
      - Pre-Institute Seminar (Wayne State) (3)
        - Films (Box 58)
        - Memoranda (Box 58)
        - Presentations (Box 58)
        - Proceedings (Box 58)
        - Proceedings Report, 1967-1968 (Box 58)
      - Printing (Box 58)
      - Printing -- Frank Gumpert (Box 58)
      - Professional Resources (2) (Box 59)
      - Programming Planning Budgeting System (PPBS), undated (Box 59)
      - Progress Reports
        - Third (Box 59)
        - Fourth (Box 59)
        - Fourth (original) (Box 59)
      - Purchase Order Information (Box 59)
      - Purchasing, General (Box 59)
      - Questionnaire and Coding (Box 59)
      - Questionnaire Responses (2) (Box 59)
      - Questionnaire Responses (Box 60)
      - Reports (2) (Box 60)
      - Reports -- Drafts (Box 60)
      - Requests for Proceedings and Films (Box 60)
      - Speech -- Robert Luke (Box 60)
      - Staffing
        - Aids and Associates (Box 60)
        - Associates (Box 60)
        - Institutes (Box 60)
        - Specialists (Box 60)
      - State Director Meeting (Box 60)
      - Technical Reports (Box 60)
      - Travelling Record of Staff Members (Box 60)
      - University Estimates for Summer Institutes (Box 60)
      - University Resources Specialist, Progress Report (Box 60)
      - University Staff Specialists (Box 60)
      - U.S. Armed Forces Institutes, Quotation (Box 60)
      - USOE (Box 60)
      - USOE Quarterly Reports (Box 60)
      - USOE Staff Meeting (Box 60)
    - 1967 Regional Institutes
      - Regional Reports (I-VIII) (Box 61)
      - Florida State University (Box 61)
      - George Washington University (Box 61)
      - Montclair State College (2) (Box 61)
      - North Carolina State University (Box 61)
      - Northern Illinois University (Box 61)
      - Portland State College (2) (Box 62)
      - State University of New York at Albany (2) (Box 62)
      - University of California at Los Angeles (2) Evaluation Report, 1967-68 (Box 62)
      - University of Colorado (2) (Box 62)
      - University of Connecticut (Box 62)
      - University of Hawaii (Box 62)
      - University of Iowa (Box 63)
      - University of Maine (2) (Box 63)
      - University of Missouri at Kansas City (2) (Box 63)
      - University of Oklahoma (Box 63)
      - University of South Carolina (Box 63)
      - University of Texas (3) (Box 64)
      - University of Wyoming (Box 64)
      - Wayne State University (Box 64)
    - 1968-1969
      - ABE Involvement (Box 64)
      - Administration (Box 64)
      - Administration, General and Memoranda (Box 64)
      - Audio-Visual (Box 64)
      - Audio-Visual Specialists (Box 64)
      - Business Concepts (Box 64)
      - Contact List (Box 64)
      - Correspondence, See also General Correspondence
        - Florida State University (Box 64)
        - George Washington University (Box 65)
        - North Carolina State University (Box 65)
        - Northern Illinois University (Box 65)
        - Nunney, Derek (Box 65)
        - Portland State College (Box 65)
        - Requests for Publications (Box 65)
        - SUNY Albany (Box 65)
        - UCLA (Box 65)
        - University of Connecticut (Box 65)
        - University of Hawaii (Box 65)
        - University of Iowa (Box 65)
        - University of Maine (Box 65)
        - University of Missouri (Box 65)
        - University of South Carolina (Box 65)
        - University of Texas (Box 65)
        - University of Wyoming (Box 65)
        - Wayne State University (Box 65)
      - Educational Psychology Associates (Box 65)
      - Evaluation
        - Evaluation (Box 65)
        - Forms--Educational Psychology Associates (Box 65)
        - Participant Evaluation (Box 65)
        - Questionnaire (Box 65)
        - Report -- Proposal (Box 65)
        - Report -- Request for Quotations (Box 65)
      - Evaluation and Final Report (originals), Vol. I and II (Box 65)
        - References (Box 66)
        - References -- Public Laws 88-452, 89-794, 1964-66 (Box 66)
      - Final Report (original), correspondence and guidelines (Box 66)
      - Finance (Box 66)
      - Follow-Up Evaluation (Box 66)
      - Follow-Up Questionnaire (Box 66)
      - General Correspondence (Box 66)
      - General Information (Box 66)
      - Grant (Box 66)
      - Information and Materials Lists (Box 66)
      - Institute Visitations (Box 66)
      - "Involving the Uninvolved in Adult Education" -- Edgar Easley (Box 66)
      - Meetings (Box 66)
      - NAPSAE (Box 66)
      - North Carolina State University (Box 66)
      - Montclair State College (Box 66)
      - Participants Survey (Box 66)
      - Programmed Instruction (Box 66)
      - Proposal (Box 66)
      - Requests for 1968 ABE Materials (Box 67)
      - Requests for Proceedings and Films (Box 67)
      - University of California (Box 67)
      - University of Texas (Box 67)
      - USOE (3) (Box 67)
  - Manuals and published material
    - National University Extension Association. Studies in University Extension Education (I-X). Bloomington, Indiana: National University Extension Association, 1943-1953. [one bound volume] (Box 67)
    - Project Head Start
      - Local Project Approval, May 1965 [2 vol.] (Box 67)
      - Manuals (Box 67)
        - Eastern Kentucky State College, 1965 (Box 67)
        - Pennsylvania State College, 1965 (Box 68)
        - Tufts University, 1965 (Box 68)
        - Universidad de Puerto Rico, 1965 (Box 69)
        - Universidad de Puerto Rico, 1965 (Box 69)
        - University of Colorado, 1965 (Box 69)
        - University of Georgia, 1965 (Box 69)
        - University of Missouri, undated (Box 69)
        - University of Tennessee, undated (Box 69)
        - Upper Iowa University, 1965 (Box 70)
        - Utah State University, 1965 (Box 70)
  - Photographs (Box 70-72)
    Three boxes of photographs from the USOE Teacher Trainer Institutes. Many but not all are labeled. Box 30 [70?] includes folders of specific regional institutes.